Previously on From...
We have to get inside!
We'll be safe in there.
I'll be right behind you.
Fuck!
Why were you
screaming like that?
I had a really bad dream.
Your mom needs you, okay?
Go and get help.
Dad!
Julie!
- No!
- Stop!
- Get inside!
- We can't just leave them!
This bitch blew out our ride
home with a fucking shotgun!
You have no idea
what you're doing.
This whole time
you've been less than
two hours away
with these people.
It isn't what you think.
Stop fucking smiling!
You'll feel better
if you come outside.
I can't fucking
do this anymore.
I know.
You shouldn't be doing this.
Victor wouldn't like it.
Every time I see something
really weird, I see this.
This symbol.
It's not safe here.
This is where they sleep.
Come on, Victor.
Go, Victor, go!
Maybe this is just gonna be like
one of those crazy stories
that we just tell at parties,
and it'll be fun and--
Is anyone in there?
Please help us.
We were on a bus.
You ever wonder
if Abby was right?
What if it's all just a dream?
Ah!
My blood is your blood now.
What do you mean it collapsed?
Which house collapsed?
The one next to the diner.
- Oh my God!
- Tabitha!
So, she pushed you
into a tree, and then you...
I-- Then I was
someplace else.
So you, like--
So, you're saying you,
like, teleported?
No, I... Maybe.
I don't know.
When you say it like that,
it sounds frickin' crazy.
Dad, where is Sara?
I don't know.
She said she was gonna
be right behind me.
So, do you think she's alive?
I don't know.
Okay, look, I need you to really
just take me through this, okay?
Look, you went through
a tree and then what?
Then I was back here.
How?
I got lucky.
I found my way. I-I--
No, look, look,
if you don't wanna tell me,
just say that you
don't wanna tell me.
- Hey.
- No, no. Dad. Dad.
You said that
you were gonna find answers.
You said you were
gonna go out there
and find answers
or find a way home!
That's what you said!
And now we're exactly
where we fucking started!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey, what's going on here?
Ellis, hey.
Talk to me.
What--
What happened?
What's happening, son?
Fatima. She, um...
Look, last night
it got bad.
Dad, it got really bad.
Yeah, I, I feel like
the people that make it here,
it's because they...
There's a part of themselves
that they hold on to.
Right.
And... I just think, you know...
Look, last night
I feel like I saw
that piece of her...
start to slip away.
I got it. Okay.
Hey, hey.
Look at me.
Then it has
to be you, okay?
You have to be that piece of her
that this place can't take away.
That's how
we get through this. Okay?
Even if we lose our way,
we hold on to each other
and we keep trying.
'Til we get home.
That's right.
This place
will not win.
You understand me?
Good.
Come here. Come.
Alright.
- Okay.
- Um...
I'm gonna go give
Kenny a hand
checking on
the animal traps and--
Let somebody else do that.
Go see Fatima.
Well, I--
You know, I figured while
I was out there I could, uh,
pick her some of those
wildflowers she likes.
- Good. Good. Good man.
- Yeah.
Hey, you know what?
You should, uh,
think about getting
her a new ring.
That little wire doo-dad, I--
Hey, you're better
than that.
Right?
I'm glad you're back, Dad.
Yeah.
" plays]
♪ When I was just a little boy ♪
♪ I asked my father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be handsome?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ Here's what he said to me ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
♪ Now I have
children of my own ♪
♪ They ask their father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be pretty?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ I tell them tenderly ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
All done. Good. You did great.
- You're okay.
- Breathe, breathe, breathe.
I'm just gonna
clip it here, okay?
Good.
Alright.
Just try to keep it dry, okay?
Yeah.
We can take them out in
probably a week or two, alright?
So, we're done here, then?
Ah, you have...
...three cracked ribs
and probably a bruised lung.
I wouldn't exactly
call that fine, okay?
You okay, Dad?
Yeah, buddy.
Just catching my breath,
that's all.
How you doing?
I... heard you had
a pretty rough night too.
She was on a quest with Victor.
I'm okay.
Um, look, bottom line is,
you got really lucky.
So just don't do anything
to make it worse, okay?
Alright.
I'll check back on you in a bit.
- Alright.
- Thank you.
Kids, can you give me
and your mom a second?
Yeah. Of course.
Donna said we could
stay at the Colony House,
but there's no way in hell
I'm taking the kids--
Tabby.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
I thought you were dead.
I'm sorry.
- I thought--
- I know. I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I can't lose you.
No, no, no.
Jim...
the wires aren't
connected to anything.
What?
Yeah, they were just
dangling from the ceiling.
How'd there be any electricity
if the wires
aren't connected?
Tabitha, we have
so much to talk about.
How are the kids holding up?
I don't know.
I think I'm gonna
take them to the diner
to see if I can get some food.
I don't know when they've eaten.
I love you.
I love you too.
You are not
listening to me.
No, I'm listening,
and I'm telling you to fuck off.
You think after
what happened last night
I'm just gonna trust you people?
That is not gonna
do any good against
those things
that come out at night!
All you're gonna do is
make everyone here nervous.
No, but it's okay for you to
start shooting out fuckin' tires
though, right? Because that made
people real fuckin' calm!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- You are a f--
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, hey, hey, Donna.
What's-- What's goin' on here?
What's goin' on, Donna?
Who the fuck are you?
Boyd Stevens.
I'm the sheriff.
I thought the Asian guy
was the sheriff.
We're just having a little
disagreement about firearms.
Residents don't carry guns.
That's the rule.
And whose rule
is that?
Mine.
Well, uh, rules change.
No, no, no.
Got it, hold, hold up.
Look. I understand.
I understand this is
all pretty scary, right?
But I've had
a strange fuckin' week,
so I'm a little less
patient than normal.
You don't like the rules. Great.
You take your rifle,
you go live out in the woods,
and make whatever
rules you like.
See how long you last.
Now, now.
You want a roof over your head
at night when those things
come out to hunt, then you put
the fucking rifle down
and you listen to the lady.
That's a good choice.
Mm.
Mm-hm.
Listen.
We're all... gonna have
the time to talk, okay?
Answer all your questions.
- Just know...
- Asshole.
...that we are all
in this thing together,
and the only way to get
through this is together.
Take 'em to the house.
Go. Go.
Do you want more?
- No, that's good.
- Okay, come on.
Okey-dokey. Here.
Honey, you need
to eat something.
I'm not hungry.
Have this, Jules.
Really good.
Can we go see Victor?
Mom?
Yeah?
Can we go see Victor?
No, honey, not now.
He's been through
a rough few days.
I hope
he's not mad at me.
Why would he
be mad at you?
Me and Jade
were in his room.
He said he was looking for
clues about how to get home.
I told him Victor
wouldn't like it.
Are we gonna be able
to get our stuff back?
Norman's down there.
I don't know, honey.
Eat your food, okay?
Where are you going?
I'll be right back.
Can I-- Can I talk
to you for a second?
Yeah.
You like tea?
Oh, no, no.
Thank you. I'm okay.
Um...
I know you oversee
a lot of the supplies in town,
and I was wondering if maybe
I could go through the storage?
Everything we had
was in that house.
We don't have any supplies
or clothing or--
You come stay our house.
Okay?
Mothers help together.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Ya hear about Kristi's fiancée?
I did.
Not sure that's
ever happened before.
So, uh, you know,
what are supplies looking like?
Not good.
Storm wiped out half our crop.
We're gonna have to get
real serious about rations
with all of the new people.
Driver said
there were 25 aboard.
What with the folks in the diner
and the bodies
we found this morning,
we're accounting
for about 22.
Busload of terrified people,
and I fire a fuckin' shotgun.
You were gonna lose
people no matter what,
so let's... focus on
the ones you saved.
You gonna tell me
what happened out there?
Hey, I got another one.
Okay.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Shit.
Can we salvage
that one?
No, there's, um...
I can't find the...
Can you stop with the flowers,
please, and just help?
Listen, man, I, uh...
I get that you're probably
all bent out of shape
about the whole Kristi thing.
Never mind.
It's fine. Uh...
Look, there's a-- there's a--
there's a rod that helps
prop up the traps.
I just-- I don't...
Okay, um--
I must've put the--
♪ Wake up, little Susie,
wake up ♪
What the hell is that?
♪ Wake up,
little Susie and weep ♪
♪ The movie's over,
it's four o'clock ♪
♪ And we're in trouble deep ♪
-♪ Wake up, little Susie ♪
- Jesus.
♪ Wake up, little Susie ♪
♪ Well, what are we
gonna tell your mama?♪
♪ What are we gonna... ♪
Okay, um, we have to bring
her back into town to bury her.
How--
Why would they do that and--
Just put the goddamn
flowers down and help me.
Right, she's, um,
look, she's--
she's pinned to the tree,
so I...
Get Kristi.
Now.
Yeah.
Go!
Help me.
Please help me.
Yeah, it's okay.
It's okay.
No, no.
No, no, no, no, no--
I'm glad you're okay.
What?
I said I'm glad you're okay.
We lost so many people,
I was worried that--
- Who was in my room?
- Sorry?
Someone was in my room,
and they took something.
Oh, um, I think I saw Jade
and the Matthews boy
up here last night. But--
Excuse me.
What? What?!
What?!
Oh, you're back.
Holy shit.
This is great. This is great.
That's mine.
- Ah.
- Give it back to me.
- Yeah. Uh--
- I'm sorry, alright.
- Give it back to me.
I was just thinking I could
just play it for a little bit--
- Give it back to me!
- Okay! Alright.
Calm down, man. Here.
That's my room!
You don't go in my room!
Okay.
Wait! Oh, hold on.
Hey! Slow down! I'm sorry.
Okay? I shouldn't have gone
in your room.
I thought you were fucking dead.
I've been looking
everywhere for you.
There's this symbol
that I keep seeing.
I mean, I keep seeing things
that aren't actually there,
but every time I do,
there's this symbol,
and there's this book
that Kenny's mom gave me.
Some guy kept drawing the same
symbol and there's a picture.
Would you please
just fucking stop!
Look at this. Look at this.
There's gotta be a reason
I'm seeing this everywhere.
This guy.
He must've been
seeing it too. Right?
And look, right there.
Right in the back.
That's you, right?
Maybe in some fucked-up way,
this could be the key to
getting the hell out of here.
I mean, Jesus, all this time.
Don't you wanna go home?
You shouldn't have touched this.
It's not yours.
Stay away from me!
Well, fuck you too!
Wait, uh-- Fuck.
Yeah, the paint got
a little faded.
First few weeks I was here,
I carried it everywhere I went.
I held it when I slept.
Sweaty palms, I guess.
I, um... I like the blonde.
It's a cute look.
I, uh... I know
all this is a lot.
But we can get
through this together.
Hey, sorry--I--
No, it's okay.
It's fine. I just...
Maybe, um...
Maybe I should stay with
the others from the bus.
People died last night,
and that's the rock I painted
for you sitting there
like it was on
your nightstand at home,
and... you're just
acting like everything's...
I just need...
I just need some time.
Kristi!
Are you in here?
It's an emergency!
Uh, coming.
Kristi! Yeah, great.
- What?
- We need your help.
- Okay.
- Now.
- What's going on?
- I gotta go.
I promise we'll talk
as soon as I'm back, okay?
- No--
- Just-- I love you.
Don't do anything
until I leave.
- Kristi--
- I gotta go.
I'm sorry.
It doesn't hurt.
That's weird, right?
Why doesn't it hurt?
Are you still there?
Yeah.
Yeah. I'm still here.
What's your name?
I'm Ellis.
Cool name.
I'm Kelly.
Hi. Hi, Kelly.
Um...
where are we?
We're, uh...
We're in the woods.
Just outside town.
The woods.
How?
Oh, God.
We were in the bar.
These people came in. They...
Brian was screaming.
It's okay. It's okay.
No. No.
No, you don't understand.
They--
They dragged us out. They...
made me watch.
They said they wanted to...
play with me.
What-- What the f--
Hey, hey.
'Kay, uh, the doctor's here.
She's gonna take
care of you, okay?
Hi.
I'm Kristi.
I'm just gonna take
a look at you, okay?
Okay.
Is it bad?
It's bad.
- Oh, God.
- Hey.
It's bad.
Hey.
Take my hand.
Squeeze it as hard
as you like.
And I'm gonna
take a look, okay?
Squeeze. Squeeze.
Good.
Oh, am I
interrupting something?
I was looking
for the doctor.
I think her name
is Kristi.
Uh...
She had to run out.
Can I, uh...
Can I help you with something?
You're the fella that
got stuck under the house.
Yeah.
That boy from the bus
that got stuck with you?
He sat across
the aisle from me.
I'll let you get back to...
Where were you headed?
You were on a bus.
Where were you going?
Oh.
The racetrack.
I was gonna bet on the ponies.
I've been visiting racetracks
all across the country.
Was it a charter bus?
Uh, I don't know.
It was a bus.
It had wheels and a door
and tickets you had to buy.
What's in the bag?
Oh.
You ask a lot of questions.
I just have one more.
Uh, we need
a little help in here!
Hey.
Hey, you're supposed
to be in bed.
Who the hell are you?
My name's Marielle.
I'm a nurse.
Let's get you
off the floor, okay?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
Okay, there we go.
Little sore.
'Kay, I'm gonna see
if I can find you
an aspirin or something.
Excuse me.
- I'll stay with him.
- Thank you.
You okay?
Oh.
Can you imagine?
Showing up in a place like this
to find out that
your fiancée is here?
What did you say?
Well, Kristi and Marielle.
They're engaged.
You're my what?
Your proxy.
It's uh, something we normally
do on the first night,
but things happened a little
differently this time.
So, if you have any questions
or if there's anything I can do
to make things a little--
How long have you been here?
Uh, just had
my one-year anniversary.
It was, um--
You good?
Is there water nearby?
Like a...
a lake or a pond?
Uh, yeah, I mean,
we have this place called
the Brundles not far from here.
Can I see it?
Here it is.
Closest thing to
normal fun we have here.
Why do they
call it the Brundles?
Uh, it was just called
that when I got here.
How did you know about--
I saw it.
Were you the one on
the bus that had the dream?
Yeah, those happen sometimes.
People have all sorts of
strange reactions to this place.
Dreams, nightmares,
weird premonitions.
But we don't know why
or what it means.
Why it happens to some people
and not to others.
This one girl, Nadia,
she used to say that it was
like this place was
calling out to us,
but only some of us were
listening closely enough
to hear it.
But has anyone--
Yes.
People have obsessed
over these things.
They've compared
and picked it apart.
It didn't tell us anything
we didn't already know.
Which is what?
That we're stuck.
And nobody can tell us why.
So?
Well, I mean,
even if we were in a hospital,
this would be at least
a 15-hour operation.
But she's talking.
I mean, she's literally
sitting there and talking.
Yeah, I know.
But, uh, how long
can she be here?
Uh, I mean, it could be hours.
It could be days.
I-- She's not
suffering right now,
but I don't know how
long that's gonna last.
Those things,
they'll be back tonight.
Okay, so then we have
to get her out of here.
Look, I don't
think you understand.
I mean, it's a miracle
she's even still alive.
So then, what do we do?
How do we, um...
How do we do it?
Do you have something
in your bag that might--
No, nothing that
would be strong enough.
We have to pull out the rod.
Okay. Will it, uh...
Will it be peaceful?
I don't know.
Look, there's...
there is one more option.
No. No.
I'm not having her last moments
be with a gun to her head, okay?
Kristi?
Hey.
I'm right here.
I'm not okay, am I?
No.
No, you're not.
Am I gonna die?
Yeah.
These are for Dad.
Mom, this has a huge hole
in it.
So? If it fits, it goes.
Oh, just like this one. Perfect.
So how come Ethan gets
to spend the afternoon
looking through
toys with Mrs. Liu
and I get stuck doing this?
Oh, honey, I'm sorry,
do you want to play with toys?
Come on, Julie.
This is what being
an adult looks like.
Hm.
Oh.
Look at this.
Try this on.
This is so creepy.
All this stuff has
belonged to people who've...
What?
It's no different
than a thrift store.
It's a little different.
It fits you. Perfect.
So are we living with
Kenny and his mom now?
And Jade?
Well, just for now.
You know, once your dad's
back on his feet,
then we can start look--
Mom?
Mom, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Mom, what happened
just now?
- What's going on?
- Wait.
I don't know.
Nothing. Let's go home.
- What?
- Let's go home.
- Come on.
- Okay, okay.
Hey, babe.
I'm back a little
sooner than expected.
That big swing we talked about?
It didn't go quite
the way I'd planned.
But I got some news. Uh...
Somebody's getting married.
Maybe you already knew that.
Or maybe...
Maybe none of this is real.
Maybe you and Ellis are
sittin' by a hospital bed
waiting for me
to open my eyes up.
Just open your eyes up! Op--
I mean, how could a--
How could a man that's
chained to a wall in a place
that's not there
know your name?
How can that be real?
That-- How can--
Mom, what happened back there?
Nothing. I'm fine.
Mom.
What?! I'm fine.
You know, why don't you
take these upstairs, please.
Mom, talk to me!
Do you know what I spent
the whole night
thinking about in that diner?
How I was gonna have to
take care of Ethan by myself,
'cause I thought you were dead.
And I sat there waiting
for those things to find Dad
and rip him apart.
So don't tell me you're fine,
and don't tell me it's nothing.
Yes, I saw something.
Something that wasn't there.
It's not the first
time that's happened.
What do you mean?
After Thomas died,
for months I could
still hear him crying.
Sometimes I would
even go into a room,
and I would see him there.
Just for a second.
It always felt so peaceful.
Like he was letting me
know he was okay.
So that's what
happened just now?
You saw Thomas?
No. No, no.
No, this... this was different.
I saw two children
standing in the middle
of the road staring at me.
But this...
What?
It didn't feel peaceful.
Is Ellis still there?
Hi.
Yeah, I'm still here.
And, um,
who's the other boy?
Oh, that's, uh...
that's Kenny.
He's our deputy.
Hi, Kenny.
Hi.
You're all so nice.
Um, can you get
my phone, please?
I have to call my mom.
I have to tell her--
Um, yeah, the, uh,
the phones here,
they... they don't really work.
But, uh, we can...
we can write you a note.
I've got some paper
in-in my bag.
You, uh... you just
tell us what you wanna say,
and we'll write it
down for you, okay?
You'll make sure she gets it?
Yeah.
I guess that'd be okay.
Whenever you're ready.
Um, tell her, um...
Tell her that I love her.
And I'm sorry
I didn't give her a hug.
Um, she wanted one,
but I was mad when I left so...
It was so stupid.
We had this fight
about Brian, um...
And I...
I didn't give her a hug,
so tell her that I'm sorry.
And, um...
What is that?
Hey.
Kelly, what's wrong?
Do you hear that? It's--
Kelly! Hey!
Hey, what's happening, Kristi?
I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know.
The longer we wait,
the more she'll suffer, okay?
Okay. Alright. I'll do it.
It's my job.
Hello! Hello?
Hey, hey! I heard screams.
She's--
She's from the bus.
They left her like that.
Kristi. Kenny. Come.
Come.
You all go back
to town now, okay?
What?
You don't need to
be here for this.
- All due respect, Sheriff--
- Kristi, I'm not asking.
I'm not leaving, okay?
Alright, alright, alright.
What's her name?
- What's her name?
- It's Kelly.
Hey, Kelly?
I can't!
I'm so-- No!
Okay.
You squeeze
my hand, okay?
Alright.
Okay, Kelly, just squeeze.
Good.
Keep squeezing.
Marielle?
Hey.
Everything okay?
Please stay.
Kristi.
Baby, what--
I just need
you to stay.
Baby, what--
I just need you to stay.
Hey.
Come here.
Hey, it's okay.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna head
over to the church.
I told Donna I'd look
through the stuff
that Father Khatri had,
see if there's something
we can read at the service.
- Yeah.
- So.
Kenny.
Yeah?
It's those things.
They did this.
Hey.
I've, uh,
been looking for you.
Sorry, I was just, um...
Promise me it won't
always be this way.
You can lie if you have to.
Just please...
promise me.
Let's get married.
What?
Look, I know that
we said we'd wait,
and, you know, that we'd
do it when we got back home,
but I... you know what?
I don't wanna wait.
I don't wanna let this place
be the thing that decides
when we get to be happy.
So let's do it.
Let's get married.
Okay.
Okay?
We're getting married.
Okay! Okay.
We're getting--
We're getting married!
Hey.
Is that from Ms. Liu?
It was in
the storage closet.
She said I could have it.
It's a puzzle.
It's so cool.
Um, I want to talk to
you about something.
Um...
I know how much you like
to see everything like a--
like a challenge or a quest.
But I just wanted
you to realize--
I know it's dangerous here.
I know it's not like things
are all just make-believe,
and I promise I'll be careful.
Good.
Hey.
I think I got it.
Cool, huh?
- Oh, my God. Stand up.
- What's wrong?
- Stand up right now. Right now.
Let's go. Get in.
Get in, get in, get in.
Oh, fuck!
Fuck!
- Hey.
Looks like you're
having a shit day too.
Yeah.
There was this, uh, girl
from the bus out in the forest.
Kelly.
Those things
dragged her out there,
and, uh, they took a metal
rod from one of the traps.
They stuck it right in
her head and into a tree.
Kid was still alive.
- Did you have to--
- Yeah.
I'm sorry, Boyd.
Ellis said she was traveling
with her boyfriend, Brian?
Those things got him.
Said they... made her watch
what they did to him.
Jesus Christ.
Funny thing, though.
My first tour in Iraq,
I was, uh...
I was driving with
a few guys from my unit
back to our command center.
We drove over an IED.
Standard-issue jeep.
The fucking thing
blew right through it.
First two guys,
dead on impact,
but there was
this kid from Wisconsin,
we used to call him Smuckers
'cause the kid
fucking loved jelly.
Anyway, the shrapnel
from the IED, right,
ripped right through.
He died in my arms.
He was crying.
Begging.
First time I ever
watched someone die.
Corporal Brian Kelly.
How about that?
That's a... that's a pretty
big fucking coincidence,
don't you think?
Brian Kelly. J--
Boyd, that's--
No, no, no. I killed a kid,
and instead of mourning,
I'm standing here trying to
figure out how any of this
shit can be fucking real!
Boyd, what happened
in the forest?
I gotta go.
Nah! No, no, no!
You do not get to walk in here
and dump a load
of shit like that
and then just walk away!
You don't wanna tell me? Fine.
You talk when
you feel like talking.
Okay.
I just need to know
that you got your shit together.
I tried doing what you do, okay?
And I just got a bunch
of fucking people killed.
Donna--
No, I don't need
a goddamn pep talk!
I just need to know
that you're back!
Because these people can't
take a whole lot more of this.
Fuck.
I'm not sure how much
more I can take.
Okay.
Hello?
Someone down here?
Hi, Kenny.